[
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "Um9sZXggaXMgYSBjb21wYW55IHRoYXQgc3BlY2lhbGl6ZXMgaW4gd2hhdCB0eXBlIG9mIHByb2R1Y3Q/",
    "correct_answer": "V2F0Y2hlcw==",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Q2Fycw==",
      "Q29tcHV0ZXJz",
      "U3BvcnRzIGVxdWlwbWVudA=="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgQW1lcmljYW4gc2luZ2VycyBhbmQgc29uZ3dyaXRlcnMgd29uIGEgTm9iZWwgUHJpemUgaW4gTGl0ZXJhdHVyZT8=",
    "correct_answer": "Qm9iIER5bGFu",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "QnVkZHkgSG9sbHk=",
      "Sm9obm55IENhc2g=",
      "QWxpY2UgQ29vcGVy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgc3RhciBzaWduIG9mIHNvbWVvbmUgYm9ybiBvbiBWYWxlbnRpbmVzIGRheT8=",
    "correct_answer": "QXF1YXJpdXM=",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "UGlzY2Vz",
      "Q2Fwcmljb3Ju",
      "U2NvcnBpbw=="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hpY2ggQW1lcmljYW4gbWFudWZhY3R1cmVkIHN1Ym1hY2hpbmUgZ3VuIHdhcyBpbmZvcm1hbGx5IGtub3duIGJ5IHRoZSBBbWVyaWNhbiBzb2xkaWVycyB0aGF0IHVzZWQgaXQgYXMgIkdyZWFzZSBHdW4iPw==",
    "correct_answer": "TTM=",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Q29sdCA5bW0=",
      "VGhvbXBzb24=",
      "TUFDLTEw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBJdnkgTGVhZ3VlIHVuaXZlcnNpdGllcyBoYXMgaXRzIG9mZmljaWFsIG1vdHRvIGluIEhlYnJldyBhcyB3ZWxsIGFzIGluIExhdGluPw==",
    "correct_answer": "WWFsZSBVbml2ZXJzaXR5",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "UHJpbmNldG9uIFVuaXZlcnNpdHk=",
      "SGFydmFyZCBVbml2ZXJzaXR5",
      "Q29sdW1iaWEgVW5pdmVyc2l0eQ=="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "T24gYXZlcmFnZSwgQW1lcmljYW5zIGNvbnN1bWUgMTAwIHBvdW5kcyBvZiB3aGF0IHBlciBzZWNvbmQ/",
    "correct_answer": "Q2hvY29sYXRl",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "UG90YXRvZXM=",
      "RG9udXRz",
      "Q29jYWluZQ=="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hhdCBmYXN0IGZvb2QgY2hhaW4gaGFzIHRoZSBtb3N0IGxvY2F0aW9ucyBnbG9iYWxseT8g",
    "correct_answer": "U3Vid2F5",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "U3RhcmJ1Y2tz",
      "TWNEb25hbGRz",
      "S0ZD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "VGhlIGxlc3Nlci1rbm93biBjb250aW51YXRpb24gb2YgdGhlIHNheWluZyAiQ3VyaW9zaXR5IGtpbGxlZCB0aGUgY2F0Li4uIiBpczo=",
    "correct_answer": "Ii4uLmJ1dCBzYXRpc2ZhY3Rpb24gYnJvdWdodCBpdCBiYWNrLiI=",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Ii4uLmFuZCB0aGUgc2lsZW50IG1vdXNlIHJlbWFpbmVkIHRoZXJlYXQuIg==",
      "Ii4uLndoaWNoIHRhdWdodCBpdCBub3QgdG8gZG8gdGhhdC4i",
      "Ii4uLmJ1dCBkZWF0aCBieSB0aGUgdHJ1dGggaXMgYmV0dGVyIHRoYW4gaWdub3JhbmNlLiI="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIHNvZnQgZHJpbmsgUGVwc2kgb3JpZ2luYWxseSBpbnRyb2R1Y2VkIGFzPw==",
    "correct_answer": "QnJhZCdzIERyaW5r",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "UGVwc2luIFBvcA==",
      "Q2Fyb2xpbmEgQ29sYQ==",
      "UGVwc2luIFN5cnVw"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "SW4gd2hhdCB5ZWFyIHdhcyBNY0RvbmFsZCdzIGZvdW5kZWQ/",
    "correct_answer": "MTk1NQ==",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "MTk2NA==",
      "MTk1MQ==",
      "MTk0Nw=="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "QWNjb3JkaW5nIHRvIHRoZSBCQlBBLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBtb3N0IGNvbW1vbiBwdWIgbmFtZSBpbiB0aGUgVUs/",
    "correct_answer": "UmVkIExpb24=",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Um95YWwgT2Fr",
      "V2hpdGUgSGFydA==",
      "S2luZydzIEhlYWQ="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "VGhlIGFyY2hpdGVjdCBrbm93biBhcyBMZSBDb3JidXNpZXIgd2FzIGFuIGltcG9ydGFudCBmaWd1cmUgaW4gd2hhdCBzdHlsZSBvZiBhcmNoaXRlY3R1cmU/",
    "correct_answer": "TW9kZXJuaXNt",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "TmVvY2xhc3NpY2Fs",
      "QmFyb3F1ZQ==",
      "R290aGljIFJldml2YWw="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "SW4gYW5jaWVudCBHcmVlY2UsIGlmIHlvdXIgam9iIHdlcmUgYSAiaGlwcGV1cyIgd2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2Ugd291bGQgeW91IG93bj8=",
    "correct_answer": "SG9yc2U=",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "V2VhdmU=",
      "R3VpdGFy",
      "Qm9hdA=="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBnaXZlbiB0byBJbmRpYW4gZm9vZCBjb29rZWQgb3ZlciBjaGFyY29hbCBpbiBhIGNsYXkgb3Zlbj8=",
    "correct_answer": "VGFuZG9vcmk=",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "QmlyeWFuaQ==",
      "UGFuaSBwdXJp",
      "VGlraSBtYXNhbGE="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "VGhlIGVhcmx5IHBhcnQgb2Ygd2hpY2ggZGVjYWRlLCBkaWQgdGhlIEdvdGggU3ViY3VsdHVyZSBiZWdpbj8=",
    "correct_answer": "MTk4MHM=",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "MTk5MHM=",
      "MjAwMHM=",
      "MTk3MHM="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hlbiB3YXMgdGhlIERlY2xhcmF0aW9uIG9mIEluZGVwZW5kZW5jZSBhcHByb3ZlZCBieSB0aGUgU2Vjb25kIENvbnRpbmVudGFsIENvbmdyZXNzPw==",
    "correct_answer": "SnVseSA0LCAxNzc2",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "TWF5IDQsIDE3NzY=",
      "SnVuZSA0LCAxNzc2",
      "SnVseSAyLCAxNzc2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgR2VybWFuIHdvcmQgZm9yICJzcG9vbiI/",
    "correct_answer": "TMO2ZmZlbA==",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "R2FiZWw=",
      "TWVzc2Vy",
      "RXNzc3TDpGJjaGVu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgZGVmaW5pbmcgY2hhcmFjdGVyaXN0aWMgb2Ygc29tZW9uZSB3aG8gaXMgZGVzY3JpYmVkIGFzIGhpcnN1dGU/",
    "correct_answer": "SGFpcnk=",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "UnVkZQ==",
      "RnVubnk=",
      "VGFsbA=="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgcG9wdWxhciBhbmltYXRyb25pYyBzaW5naW5nIGZpc2ggcHJvcCwgc2luZ2luZyBzdWNoIGhpdHMgc3VjaCBhcyAiRG9uJ3QgV29ycnksIEJlIEhhcHB5Ij8=",
    "correct_answer": "QmlnIE1vdXRoIEJpbGx5IEJhc3M=",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "QmlnIEJpbGx5IEJhc3M=",
      "U2luZ2luZyBGaXNo",
      "U2FyZGVlbg=="
    ]
  },
  {
    "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
    "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
    "category": "R2VuZXJhbCBLbm93bGVkZ2U=",
    "question": "V2hhdCBkaWQgdGhlIFNwYW5pc2ggYXV0b25vbW91cyBjb21tdW5pdHkgb2YgQ2F0YWxvbmlhIGJhbiBpbiAyMDEwLCB0aGF0IHRvb2sgZWZmZWN0IGluIDIwMTI/",
    "correct_answer": "QnVsbGZpZ2h0aW5n",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Rmllc3Rhcw==",
      "RmxhbWVuY28=",
      "TWFyaWFjaGk="
    ]
  }
]